<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BloodBuddy</string>
    <string name="app_intro">Welcome to Bloodbuddy App</string>
    <string name="app_tutorial">Input your blood count results to obtain a meaningful info of what this result really mean!</string>
    <string name="app_tutorial2">No worries! This app will explain everything you need!</string>
    <string name="app_intro2">Do you have any idea of what your blood work results really mean?</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_header">DISCLAIMER!</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_summary">By using this application, I agree to have knowledge of the following:
I am aware that this application was created by students for a class project.
I am aware that in no way is the information on this application a substitute for medical information obtained from visiting a medical professional.
I am aware that this application is intended for informational purposes, and not to be used as sound medical advice.
I am aware that this application has no support staff of medical professionals to assist with any medical questions.
I am aware that if I choose to follow the information provided by this application, which may or may not be completey accurate, I
do so assuming full responsibilities of the consequences that result.
I will not hold the creators of this application responsible if any harm befalls on me as a result of misinformation from this application.</string>

    <string name="test_info">null</string>
    <string name="check_result_button">Check Result</string>
    <string name="radio_male">Male</string>
    <string name="radio_female">Female</string>
    <string name="intro_text">Follow these 3 easy steps to anylize your\nblood work results:\n  1. Grap your blood work report.\n  2. Read and accept the app disclaimer.\n  3. Press the floating button to start entering your blood work data!</string>


    <string-array name="testUnits_array">
        <item>Thousands/uL</item>
        <item>Millons/uL</item>
        <item>grams/dL</item>
        <item>%</item>
        <item>fL</item>
        <item>pg</item>
        <item>g/dL</item>
        <item>%</item>
        <item>Thousands/uL</item>
        <item>fL</item>
        <item>%</item>
        <item>%</item>
        <item>%</item>
        <item>%</item>
        <item>%</item>
        <item>Thousands/uL</item>
        <item>Thousands/uL</item>
        <item>Thousands/uL</item>
        <item>Thousands/uL</item>
        <item>Thousands/uL</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="tests_array">
        <item>WBC</item>
        <item>RBC</item>
        <item>HGB</item>
        <item>HCT</item>
        <item>MCV</item>
        <item>MCH</item>
        <item>MCHC</item>
        <item>RDW</item>
        <item>PLT</item>
        <item>MPV</item>
        <item>NEUT %</item>
        <item>LYMPH %</item>
        <item>MONO %</item>
        <item>EOS %</item>
        <item>BASO %</item>
        <item>NEUT,ABS</item>
        <item>LYMPH,ABS</item>
        <item>MONO,ABS</item>
        <item>EOS,ABS</item>
        <item>BASO,ABS</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="testsInfo_array">
        <item>WBC stands for white blood cells. White blood cells have the function of protecting the
            body from invaders like germs. Not having enough white blood cells can mean that a simple
            speak of dust would kill you. There are millions of white blood cells around your body.
            This test counts those white cells.</item>
        <item>RBC stands for Red Blood Cells. Red blood cells carry oxygen from the
            lungs to the rest of the body. They also carry carbon dioxide back to the lungs
            so it can be exhaled. If the RBC count is low (anemia), the body may not be getting the oxygen it needs. If the count is too high (a condition called polycythemia), there is a chance that the red blood cells will clump together and block tiny blood vessels (capillaries). This also makes it hard for your red blood cells to carry oxygen. Red blood cells carry oxygen from the lungs to the rest of the body. They also carry carbon dioxide back to the lungs so it can be exhaled. If the RBC count is low (anemia), the body may not be getting the oxygen it needs. If the count is too high (a condition called polycythemia), there is a chance that the red blood cells will
            clump together and block tiny blood vessels (capillaries). This also makes it hard for your red blood cells to carry oxygen.</item>
        <item>Hemoglobin is the protein that enables oxygen to bind to red blood cells. This protein
            gives red cells their characteristic color. Without hemoglobin, red cells cannot do their
            job of bringing oxygen around the body. One can have a high amount of red cells and still
            have diminished oxygen carrying capacity if there is little hemoglobin in the body. This
            value is tested for due to the need to know the status of ones oxygen carrying capacity.
            This value often correlates to RBC levels.</item>
        <item>A hematocrit measures the percentage of whole blood that is made up of red cells. Whole
            blood is made up of red blood cells, various types of white blood cells, platelets, and
            plasma. Plasma is the amber fluid in which your blood cells are suspended. Plasma is
            usually invisible due to the high amount of red cells that obscure amber color of the
            plasma. When blood is spun through a centrifuge, the plasma becomes visible. The test
            is done as a quick way to evaluate the ratio between red cells to the rest of the blood. </item>
        <item>MCV measures the average volume of red cells or how large or small your red cells are.
            When one has cells that are too large or too small, this can correlate to other health
            conditions. When cells are too large, they are known as macrocytic and when cells are
            too small they are known as microcytic. Cells being too large or small are problematic
            because it can skew important measurements such as hemoglobin or hematocrit measurements.
            Value can be roughly calculated by diciding Hct by RBC count. This value should mirror
            mean corpuscular hemoglobin (MCH). </item>
        <item>MCH stands for mean cell hemoglobin and measures the average weight of hemoglobin in an
            individual red cell. This is in contrast to Hgb which measures total hemoglobin in the body.
            This value can be roughly calculated by dividing Hgb by the RBC count and converting to
            appropriate units. </item>
        <item>MCHC stands for mean cell hemoglobin concentrationMean cell hemoglobin concentration
            is a measure of the average concentration of hemoglobin in each cell. Hemoglobin is the
            molecule that carries oxygen throughout the body. If cells do not have the appropriate
            amount of hemoglobin, oxygen does not get to where it needs to be. </item>
        <item>The red cell distribution width is not always reported, but it is used when a physician
            wants to know the uniformity of the size of a patients red blood cells. Red cells that
            have great variation in their size can indicate more serious health conditions. </item>
        <item>PLT stands for platelets. Platelets are little bits and pieces inside your blood that helop
            your blood to clot. Without platelets, a simple cut could kill you. You would just keep bleeding
            until you died. You can see this process at work when you get a cut. Your platelets are what
            help you form a scab. </item>
        <item>MPV stands for mean platelet volume. Platelet count is extremely important to your clotting,
            but just as important is how big the platelets are. This test measures the average size of your
            platelets.</item>
        <item>NEUT % stands for neutrophil percentage. You may have learned in school that you have red blood cells and
            white blood cells. What you may not have learned is that white blood cells are broken up further
            into several types of white blood cells. Neutrophils are one type of white blood cell. If you think of your immune
            system as an army, then you can think of neutrophils as the foot soldiers of the army. They are the most common white blood
            cell, and they are seen most often at places where infections take place. How they work is they "eat"
            the invading germs and self destruct with the invaders inside, killing the invaders. This parameter is the neutrophil
            percentage rather than the amount of neutrophils total. This means that all white blood cell percentages should
            add to 100.</item>
        <item>LYMPH % stands for lymphocyte percentage. You may have learned in school that you have red blood cells and
            white blood cells. What you may not have learned is that white blood cells are broken up further
            into several types of white blood cells. Lymphocytes are a type of white blood cell. If you think of your immune
            system as an army, then you can think of lymphocytes as the special forces. They are fewer in number, but they
            provide vital services to your immune system. They differ in function from gathering intelligence on the enemy to
            acting as a police force to seek out infected cells to telling your immune cells what to do. Without them, your immune
            system could not function. The dreaded HIV virus attacks these cells, and that is why the disease is so deadly. This
            test measures for the percentage of lymphocytes relative to the amount of other white cells in the body.</item>
        <item>MONO % stands for monocyte percentage. You may have learned in school that you have red blood cells and
            white blood cells. What you may not have learned is that white blood cells are broken up further
            into several types of white blood cells. Monocytes are a type of white blood cell. They are also known by their common name,
            the macrophage. If you think of your system, the system that protects your body from invaders, as an army, then you can
            think of monocytes as the generals of the army. Monocytes have a wide variety of functions, but their primary function
            is to call other white blood cells. They can perform some of the same functions as other white blood cells, but only they
            can command the army. This test measures the percentage of monocytes in the body relative to the amount of other white
            blood cells. </item>
        <item>EOS % stands for eosinophil percentage. You may have learned in school that you have red blood cells and
            white blood cells. What you may not have learned is that white blood cells are broken up further
            into several types of white blood cells. In the modern day, eosinophils seem not serve much of a function.
            It is theorized that they are there to protect against parasites. In the modern world, very few people have parasites,
            so these cells sometimes "over-react." Having a lot of eosinophils corresponds to having allergies. This test measures
            the percentage of eosinophils relative to the amount of other white blood cells in the body.</item>
        <item>BASO % stands for basophil percentage. You may have learned in school that you have red blood cells and
            white blood cells. What you may not have learned is that white blood cells are broken up further
            into several types of white blood cells. Basophils have been attributed to allergic reations but not as much as
            eosinophils. They are primarily involved in helping the immune system function by releasing signals which activate
            other cells. This test measures the percentage of basophils relative to the amount of other white cells in the body.
            </item>
        <item>NEUT,ABS stands for neutrophil absolute. You may have learned in school that you have red blood cells and
            white blood cells. What you may not have learned is that white blood cells are broken up further
            into several types of white blood cells. Neutrophils are one type of white blood cell. If you think of your immune
            system as an army, then you can think of neutrophils as the foot soldiers of the army. They are the most common white blood
            cell, and they are seen most often at places where infections take place. How they work is they "eat"
            the invading germs and self destruct with the invaders inside, killing the invaders. This test measures the exact amount
            of neutrophils in your body.</item>
        <item>LYMPH,ABS stands for neutrophil absolute. You may have learned in school that you have red blood cells and
            white blood cells. What you may not have learned is that white blood cells are broken up further
            into several types of white blood cells. Lymphocytes are a type of white blood cell. If you think of your immune
            system as an army, then you can think of lymphocytes as the special forces. They are fewer in number, but they
            provide vital services to your immune system. They differ in function from gathering intelligence on the enemy to
            acting as a police force to seek out infected cells to telling your immune cells what to do. Without them, your immune
            system could not function. The dreaded HIV virus attacks these cells, and that is why the disease is so deadly.
            This test measures the exact amount of lymphocytes in your body. </item>
        <item>MONO,ABS stands for monocyte absolute. You may have learned in school that you have red blood cells and
            white blood cells. What you may not have learned is that white blood cells are broken up further
            into several types of white blood cells. Monocytes are a type of white blood cell. They are also known by their common name,
            the macrophage. If you think of your system, the system that protects your body from invaders, as an army, then you can
            think of monocytes as the generals of the army. Monocytes have a wide variety of functions, but their primary function
            is to call other white blood cells. They can perform some of the same functions as other white blood cells, but only they
            can command the army. This test measures the exact amount of monocytes in the body. </item>
        <item>EOS,ABS stands for eosinophil absolute. You may have learned in school that you have red blood cells and
            white blood cells. What you may not have learned is that white blood cells are broken up further
            into several types of white blood cells. In the modern day, eosinophils seem not serve much of a function.
            It is theorized that they are there to protect against parasites. In the modern world, very few people have parasites,
            so these cells sometimes "over-react." Having a lot of eosinophils corresponds to having allergies. This test measures
            for the exact or absolute amount of eosinophils in the body. </item>
        <item>BASO,ABS stands for basophil absolute. You may have learned in school that you have red blood cells and
            white blood cells. What you may not have learned is that white blood cells are broken up further
            into several types of white blood cells. Basophils have been attributed to allergic reations but not as much as
            eosinophils. They are primarily involved in helping the immune system function by releasing signals which activate
            other cells. This test measures the absolute or exact amount of eosinophils in the body. </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
